Kobiljon Toshnazarov

1008, 100 High-Tech building Inha-ro, Nam-Gu Incheon South Korea +8210 5034 2705 kobiljon@nsl.inha.ac.kr linkedin.com/in/qobiljon

OBJECTIVE:

A challenging software engineering position that deeply utilizes algorithms and critical thinking (i.e., Android/iOS Software Engineering, Web Back-End Engineering, Microservices Engineering, etc.)

SUMMARY:

Gained exposure to key concepts of Computer Science and Engineering as a graduate researcher in the Networked Systems Lab¹. Also, prior to graduate school, gained professional experience in industry by working as a Software Engineer in IUTLab², and conducting a club of programmer students in Inha University in Tashkent.

SKILLS / KEYWORDS:

- C++ (from 98 till 17), Java (7, 8), Python, C#, SQL
- Git, Docker, Adobe Photoshop, Latex, OS proficiency (Mac OS, Windows, Linux), gRPC, Research
- Algorithms (problem solving), Android application development, Microservices, Django (REST APIs), Ionic (TypeScript)
- Confidence, Time management, Focus, Friendliness and manners, Work ethics, Public speaking

EDUCATION:

- Bachelor's Degree, 2018, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.42 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY in Tashkent (IUT), Uzbekistan
- Master's Degree, 2020, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.86 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY, Incheon, South Korea

EXPERIENCE:

Graduate Research Assistant, Networking Systems Lab in INHA University, South Korea, full-time 2018-Present Involved in research projects:

- EasyTrack (conference MobiSys 2019) a large scale sensor data collection platform for researchers
- IMSP (conference KICS 2020)
- STDD (IEEE Sensors journal paper 2020)
- MindForecaster (conference CHI 2020) mobile application to help users prepare for stressful events using personalized interventions
- <u>SNMP/GOOSE</u> KERI³ network failure monitoring platform, in collaboration with KERI (outsourced project)
- 오늘하루 A cognitive behavioral therapy program to improve various psychological difficulties (outsourced project)
- etc

Lecture Assistant in INHA University, South Korea, part-time 2018-2019

- Conducted laboratory courses for Application Programming in Java (201802CSE2107001, and 201901CSE2107001)
- Conducted laboratory courses for ComputerNetworks (201902CSE4202001)

Software Engineer, IUTLab Tashkent, Uzbekistan, part-time 2016-2017

- Developed Windows and Android client applications (i.e., <u>Kadrlar</u>, <u>MindWind</u>, etc.)
- Used tools C#, Java, Maven, PostgreSQL, Git, Firebase, Android Studio, Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio

PC & Mobile Phone Repair Assistant Technician, Kashkadarya Uzbekistan, part-time 2009-2011

- Repaired mobile phones (hardware and software)
- Did OS installations (Windows XP)
- Assembled / disassembled PCs and mobile phones

LANGUAGE SKILLS:

English - fluent (active IELTS 7.5 / 9)

Russian & Uzbek - bilingual (native)

Korean - intermediate (able to conduct non-complex conversations)

PUBLICATIONS:

- EasyTrack Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies (2019), MobiSys'19 Proceedings
- IMSP an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection (2020), KICS Winter Conference 2020 (under publication)
- Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management (2019), CHI'20 Proceedings (under publication)

_

¹ nsl.inha.ac.kr (INHA University, South Korea)

² jutlab.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)

³ Korean Electricity Research Institute